# Lidia Pulido Lopez

#### **Profile**

A highly motivated and reliable call center operative with five years' experience in a variety of customer service departments. Focused on providing a first-class customer experience and resolving any queries, complications, or issues that may arise. An excellent communicator with a confident telephone manner and customer service. An enthusiastic approach combined with genuine warmth and dedication to customer satisfaction inspires confidence in the customer and among colleagues.

## **Experience**

## GENERAL ASSISTANT 07/2019 to 03/2021

Hammerson PLC, London, UK

<u>Duties</u>: Assisting with the preparation of and the serving of all meals and beverages to customers, ensuring great customer service at all times. Using the till, serve customers, and cash up at the end of service. Check stock levels and replenish when necessary. Ensure good knowledge of products on sale and on special offers. Ensuring that the kitchen and service areas are clean and tidy, assisting with waste removal and washing up. Ensuring health and safety regulations are followed. Completing any administration as requested including food temperatures, wastage, and cleaning schedules. Assisting in the effective management of stock and portion control. To raise any issues or customer suggestions and complaints to the Catering Manager. Assist with the ordering and deliveries as required. Preparation of all hospitality request. Keep a record of all hospitality delivered and ensure it is all collected at the stated time. Ensure hospitality rooms are left tidy. Promote good teamwork and work in a friendly environment.

#### **CLIENT SUPPORT** 09/2018 to 07/2019

Lexington Catering, London, UK

<u>Duties</u>: Assisting in the delivery of events and hospitality across the sites including setting up, stewarding, and break down. Silver Service Waitressing, Serving of food and beverages, and preparation and serving of alcoholic drinks. Cash handling.

<u>Event Locations</u>: Royal Bank of Canada, Bryan Cave Leighton Paisner, Dentons, Silicon Valley Bank, Slaughter and May, Virgin Active Notting Hill and Mill Hill, London Business School, JLL, Rothschild, Hammerson, Schroders, Thomas Miller, Kirkland and Ellis, Royal London, Omnicom, Wedlake Bell, Triborough Lisson, Capital International.

#### **ASSISTANT MANAGER** 02/2017 to 07/2018

Jamon Jamon, London, UK

<u>Duties</u>: customer service and support, floor organization and setting up the tables, managing reservations and Events. Controlling stock of goods and inventory. Using the till serving customers and cash up at the end of service. Till handling and closures of shifts.

## GENERAL ASSISTANT 09/2016 to 02/2017

Evolve Hospitality, London, UK

<u>Duties</u>: Assisting in the delivery of events and hospitality across the sites including setting up, stewarding, and break down. Silver Service Waitressing, Serving of food and beverages, and preparation and serving of alcoholic drinks. Cash handling. Stocking.

Event Locations: 02 Arena, Wembley Stadium, Olympic Stadium, Twickenham Stadium, FinsburySquare.

#### CALL CENTRE AGENT 08/2014 to 08/2016

## Financiera El Corte Ingles, Madrid, Spain

<u>Duties</u>: Call-Center and Recoveries. Customer service and account management. Company administration. Receiving and dealing with all initial customer communications. Providing accurate information and advice. Guiding all customer issues to a satisfactory conclusion. Following up on ongoing customer cases and communicating progress to management and customer.

#### ACCOUNTS ADMINISTRATOR 05/2010 to 05/2014

Center-Sat, Barcelona, Spain

<u>Duties</u>: Financial management of the company, accounting, and management of goods, customer services. Answering phones and dealing with initial inquiries. Re-directing calls to appropriate departments. Maintaining customer satisfaction. Keeping customers informed of progress via email.

## Skills and Competencies

- Efficient customer service
- Self-motivated
- Team player
- Competent
- Adaptability and flexibility
- · Communicational skills
- Good time management

- Team worker
- Excellent organizational skills
- Empathic
- Committed
- IT skills: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Internet, Prezi, Mac
- IT skills coding: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python Beginner, PHP, SQL, React, API, Java, C#, GitHub
- Strong organizational, administrative, and interpersonal skills

- Workload and time management
- Excellent telephone manner
- Dedicated, driven, and proactive
- Confident communicator
- Supportive of junior staff members
- Able to remain calm in challenging situations
- Broad knowledge of computer operating systems and proficient keyboard skills

## Education

IT Career Switch. London

Feb 2021 - Actually - Web Developer Course Outline

ISPE, Spain

HND - Protocol & Organisation of Events, Protocol & Organisation of Events, 2017

Centre Roca, Spain

HND - Social Integration Studies, Social Integration, 2010

**UNED**, Spain **BA**, **Social Work** 

### Languages

Spanish (native) English (intermediate) Catalan (native)